<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<video>
    <resources><![CDATA[<p>There are no resources in this course.</p>]]>
    </resources>
    <transcript><![CDATA[
		<p><b>Coach: </b>Now, let’s see things from the Sales Manager’s perspective. Our Sales Manager shares why he seems to be losing track of his team’s performance.</p>
		
		<p><b>Manager: </b>I suppose for all of us planning and filling in reports can seem like time-consuming and unnecessary – it takes us away from the real business of meeting customers and making sales.</p>
		
		<p>Maya was unable to manage her own sales activity. She had no idea where she was in terms of the targets we had set at the start of the year, and she certainly did not know how much she was going to earn. </p>
		
		<p>Without this discipline across the whole team, I was unable to keep track of my unit targets. I would receive about two-thirds of the information, but without the final third the picture was very disjointed and I had no idea where we were at, and importantly where we were going.</p>
		
		<p>I did not know how best to help the life insurance professionals. I could not spot any patterns or trends as there were huge gaps in the figures they gave me. I didn’t know where in the sales process they needed attention. Prospecting? First Meeting? Phone calls?</p>
		
		<p>I decided to tackle the problem head on. So I got the team together and they all said they knew it was important. Of course, I did not take them at face value so I sat down individually and went through things from their perspective and mine.</p>
		
		<p>I have to say, it really made a difference. They all said it was important and they were going to do it, but I had to be really demanding to make them follow through.</p>

		<p>But they soon realized filling the activity reports wasn’t so difficult.</p>
		
		<p>Once they knew where they stood, they could plan with much more certainty and ultimately they knew how much they would earn.</p>
		
		<p>In fact, some of them have really taken to the challenge of analyzing their own figures and take corrective measures. </p>
		
		<p>It makes their time and effort much more focused, and of course it makes my targets much easier to put together.</p>

		<p>As we can see, from the Sales Manager’s point of view, he was unable to help the life insurance professionals with their problems without the activity reports. </p>

		<p>Without the inputs, it was difficult to identify strengths and development needs. It also affected the bigger picture of the team’s performance and damaged the sales performance ratio for the whole unit</p>

		<p>By tackling this problem head on with each individual life insurance professional, the sales manager was able to pull things together and take control of exactly what was happening in the whole unit.</p>
    ]]>
    </transcript>
</video>
