<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<video>
    <resources><![CDATA[<p>There are no resources in this course.</p>]]>
    </resources>
    <transcript><![CDATA[
		<p><b>Coach: </b>There are two critical indicators you should be following here. The first is sales performance ratio and the second is persistency. The sales performance ratios tell you how well an individual is performing at the key stages of the sales process. These ratios would depend upon the skill and experience of your team member.</p>
		<p>For example,<br>
			•	Prospecting to phone call              50%  <br>  
			•	Phone call to first meeting            40% <br>
			•	First meeting to second meeting        80%<br>
			•	Second meeting to sale                 25%<br>

		</p>

		<p>Once the individual sales targets for the year have been set, you can look at the implications for sales performance ratios for each stage of the sales process. </p>
		
		<p>You may find it useful to work backwards through the sales performance ratios to indicate the level of activity required. For example, for 3 sales per month, the life insurance professional will need 12 second meetings, 15 first meetings, 38 phone calls or appointments, and 76 prospects. </p>

		<p>While these targets may look difficult, you need to make just 2 calls per day to achieve the target of 38 phone calls in a month, assuming there are 25 working days in a month.

</p>
		<p>The second indicator, persistency, needs to be kept high as low levels would mean the life insurance professionals would need to work harder to replenish the lapsed clients from their portfolio. A high persistency rate comes from having good quality prospects.</p>

		<p><b>Sales Manager: </b>Now, as discussed, you will have to sell at least 10 policies in each of the next three quarters. Which means, a monthly target of 4 polices. Do you agree?</p>
		<p><b>Life insurance professional: </b>Yes, that’s right.</p>
		
		<p><b>Sales Manager: </b>Now, as per your sales performance ratios, to make 4 sales in a month, you need to hold at least 16 second meetings with potential customers. To get to 16 second meetings, you need to hold at least 20 first meetings. And to hold 20 first meetings, you need to make at least 50 phone calls. To get to 50 phone calls, you need at least 100 prospects.</p>
		<p><b>Life insurance professional: </b>That’s too many phone calls! </p>
		<p><b>Sales Manager: </b>Not really. Let’s assume there are 25 working days in the month. All you need to do is to make 4 calls per day from your Prospect List. Does that sound doable?</p>
		<p><b>Life insurance professional: </b>Yes, now it does.</p>
		<p><b>Sales Manager: </b>Great! So, let’s agree on the action plan. You will need to make a list of prospects to contact and update the Sales Activity Report on a weekly basis. You will record the number of phone calls, first meetings, second meetings and closures and share the report with me on a weekly basis.</p>
		<p><b>Life insurance professional: </b>Ok.</p>
		<p><b>Sales Manager: </b>If you need any help to achieve your target, please feel free to call me.</p>
		<p><b>Life insurance professional: </b>Thank you. I will.</p>
		
    ]]>
    </transcript>
</video>
