<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<video>
    <resources><![CDATA[<p>There are no resources in this course.</p>]]>
    </resources>
    <transcript><![CDATA[
		<p><b>Coach: </b>After you have reviewed past performance, you are now in a position to agree on monthly targets with your life insurance professionals. You will already have in mind a figure as a sales target for the month for individual life insurance professionals. </p>
		
		<p>In this section, we will show you the key factors to consider when planning performance. We will also show you how to conduct an effective one-to-one planning meeting with your life insurance professionals.</p>
		
		<p>Next, we will see a scenario to understand how the Sales Manager sets the individual sales target. </p>

		<p><b>Coach: </b>In this scenario, the Sales Manager is meeting with the life insurance professional to review the past quarter’s performance and agree on the revised individual sales target. </p>

		<p><b>Sales Manager: </b>If you recall, during our first one-to-one meeting we had decided that to achieve your personal goal for the year, you need to sell 36 policies. </p>

		<p>Now last quarter you sold a total of six policies, at an average of two policies a month against the target of three policies a month. How do you feel about your business achievement so far? </p>

		<p><b>Life insurance professional: </b>Not bad actually but I know I am short of my overall targets. I think I should be able to cover the shortfall in this quarter. </p>

		<p><b>Sales Manager: </b>Good. Now what I want is to look forward and see what you need to do to achieve your overall targets for the quarter and year. We need to stick to our plan of three policies per month and nine policies per quarter. In addition, we will need to sell one policy per quarter to cover the shortfall of the past quarter. This means we have to sell at least 10 policies in each of the next three quarters, which I know sounds quite challenging but I will support you in achieving this and I’m confident you can do it. </p>

		<p><b>Life insurance professional: </b>Well, I think I can do that. So that works out to be three second meetings a week.</p>

		<p><b>Sales Manager: </b>Absolutely. Let’s have a look at how this breaks down into your key sales activities such as sales performance ratios and persistency. </p>

		<p><b>Coach: </b>At this point the Sales Manager discusses in detail with the life insurance professional exactly what sales activity he needs to be doing. This means how many prospects he needs to call and how many first meetings he needs to have. You can’t do any of this until you decide how many sales he needs to close down each month.</p>

		<p></p>

		<p></p>
    ]]>
    </transcript>
</video>
