<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<video>
    <resources><![CDATA[<p>There are no resources in this course.</p>]]>
    </resources>
    <transcript><![CDATA[
		<p><b>Coach: </b>To plan and distribute overall sales targets among your team members, you need to hold one-to-one meetings with each life insurance professional.</p>
		
		<p>The purpose of the one-to-one planning meeting is to set and agree on achievable sales activity targets and to set up the working relationship between you and each of your life insurance professionals. You do this at the beginning of the month by sitting down with each life insurance professional. </p>
		
		<p>The one-to-one planning meeting looks at personal goals, income expectations, individual targets and performance, as well as coaching and training requirements.</p>

		<p>The first step is to spend some time discovering each life insurance professional’s personal goals. You want to understand what drives your life insurance professionals and what they hope to achieve. Centre the conversation on goals, aspirations and dreams. The areas you want to discover are: <br>
			•	Family goals <br>
			•	Professional goals <br>
			•	Lifestyle goals <br>
			•	Personal goals or dreams <br>

		</p>
		
		<p>Many of these goals, aspirations and dreams depend to a large extent on being successful professionally and financially. </p>

		<p>As their manager, you are interested in all aspects of what each life insurance professional wants to achieve, but you are particularly interested in anything that will directly drive targets.</p>

		<p>After you have found out about your life insurance professional’s personal goals, you will need to translate these into income expectations.</p>

		<p>Make sure you ask specifically about the life insurance professional’s income expectations and assess these in line with their living costs.</p>

		<p>By linking personal goals and income expectations, you can drive the individual’s performance and commitment to meet the sales targets. The aim is to create buy-in.</p>

		<p>The one-to-one planning meeting is all about discussing goals, setting targets and agreeing to activities and aspirations. During the one-to-one planning meeting, the Sales Manager must: 
			•	Learn about the life insurance professional’s personal goals by asking open questions,
			•	Encourage the life insurance professional to think about his or her own long-term goals,
			•	Get an idea about the life insurance professional’s income expectations,
			•	Talk about personal income expectations and
			•	Discuss his or her current level of achievement against the goal.

		</p>
		
    ]]>
    </transcript>
</video>
