<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<video>
    <resources><![CDATA[<p>There are no resources in this course.</p>]]>
    </resources>
    <transcript><![CDATA[
		<p>Performance measurement is about what happens in the time between your one-to-one planning meetings and subsequent quarterly review meetings with each life insurance professional. The one-to-one planning meeting has outlined a number of actions and activities. Once you have had a meeting with each of your life insurance professionals you can begin to monitor and measure their performance.</p>
		
		<p>Life insurance professionals must know how their performance is to be measured. Use clear, credible measures of performance for your team and individual life insurance professionals. The <b>sales process ratios </b>and <b>persistency ratio</b> give you the tools to measure your life insurance professionals’ performance. You need to track and measure performance on a weekly basis.</p>
		
		<p>Performance measurement takes place throughout the year. </p>

		<p>In a performance-driven culture, you need to set targets and those targets need to be managed and measured. This means as a Sales Manager you should be able to draw a line at any point over the current twelve-month period to look at performance and assess where the life insurance professional is. The performance achieved and the development required depends on the individual life insurance professionals and their sales performance. </p>
		<p>Measurement is based on the weekly Business MIS reports. </p>
		<p>If there are worrying results for a life insurance professional, you may need to schedule in additional assessments and one-to-one meetings to support the life insurance professional.</p>
		<p>You will have diarized quarterly review meetings with each of your life insurance professionals in their one-to-one planning meeting. You will also have scheduled assessment meetings for the next two to three months. These regular scheduled assessments will give you a further opportunity to measure the life insurance professional’s success. This is followed by your Needs Analysis of the life insurance professional for each stage of the sales process.</p>
		<p>The scheduled one-to-one meetings are very important as a way of checking levels of motivation, reviewing performance, agreeing  on development plans, and discussing any other issues of concern.</p>
		<p>Throughout the year there will be training and coaching interventions. This will also help with monitoring the progress and performance of each life insurance professional.</p>
    ]]>
    </transcript>
</video>
