<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<video>
    <resources><![CDATA[<p>There are no resources in this course.</p>]]>
    </resources>
    <transcript><![CDATA[
		<p><b>Coach: </b>The first thing that needs to happen when planning performance is to establish your overall annual target.</p>
		
		<p>You have to monitor performance on a monthly basis as this gives you an estimate to calculate your sales targets for the year. An essential part of your role as a Sales Manager is to contribute to the growth of your team and your Unit. </p>
		
		<p>This gives your team of life insurance professionals an opportunity to monitor their monthly performance and increase their income. It also gives you a chance to grow and increase your income.</p>

		<p>The next thing you need to consider is how to distribute your overall targets across your team of life insurance professionals. Remember that every team member will have different levels of contribution to these targets. 
		To plan and set individual targets, you need to: <br>
		•	Know your life insurance professionals well and know what they can achieve, <br>
		•	Have evidence of previous performance to make an informed decision, and <br>
		•	Come up with a figure for the discussion and agreement with each individual life insurance professional. <br>

		</p>

		<p>There are four key factors that you need to consider when planning individual targets.<br>
		1.	The <b>first</b> is your team’s structure in terms of size and experience. How big is your team? How many new life insurance professionals do you need to recruit? When should you be recruiting them? How much will they contribute towards meeting the overall targets? How experienced are the existing life insurance professionals? What has been their contribution in the past? <br>
		2.	The <b>second</b> is the minimum individual performance level. Are all of the existing individuals in your team up to the minimum performance levels? How could you help those not achieving these performance levels? How about your new life insurance professionals? How close are they to achieving the minimum performance levels? What training, coaching and support do they need? <br>
		3.	The <b>third</b> is the previous quarter’s performance. How well did each life insurance professional do the last quarter? Are your top performers likely to be able to repeat the same performance as last quarter? How will your new life insurance professionals progress this quarter? Is this the right time for them to take a larger proportion of the team’s targets? <br>
		4.	<b>Finally</b>, you need to consider your personal goals. If your team does more business and earns more, so do you. So how much do you want to earn? What are your goals for the coming year? What can you do to make sure your life insurance professionals meet or, even better, exceed those targets?<br>

		</p>
    ]]>
    </transcript>
</video>
