<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<video>
    <resources><![CDATA[<p>There are no resources in this course.</p>]]>
    </resources>
    <transcript><![CDATA[
        <p><b>Coach:</b> Performance management is about:<br>
            •   Managing individual performance, and<br>
            •   Managing team performance<br>

        </p>

        <p>Recruitment, selection, and performance planning and measurement are the key activities expected from you as a Sales Manager along with adhering to the defined sales process.</p>

        <p>The majority of performance management will be about managing the performance of individuals within your team. Over time, you will notice that there is a process to follow, which is a continuous cycle</p>

        <p>For each life insurance professional in your team, you need to:<br>
            1.  Make a fair and objective <b>assessment</b> of each individual’s current performance.<br>
            2.  Conduct effective individual <b>one-to-one meetings</b> to give feedback and agree on appropriate development targets. <br>
            3.  Deliver the appropriate <b>coaching</b> required to help the life insurance professional improve performance.<br>
            4.  Monitor and review the improvements the life insurance professional is making on an individual basis.<br>

        </p>

        <p>Managing performance should be a partnership between you and each life insurance professional to help him or her get better at what they do.</p>

        <p>There will be times when you will find common development needs for your team members. There are two ways of dealing with these needs:<br>
        1.  By conducting specific <b>training</b> sessions, which build the skills and knowledge of your life insurance professionals, and<br>
        2.  By holding regular <b>team meetings</b>, which provide an opportunity to recognise top performers and motivate them. Team meetings also provide a platform for sharing information and best practices.<br>
        </p>

        <p>Performance management allows you to <b>set</b>, <b>agree on</b> and <b>review</b> targets for development.</p>

        
        ]]>
    </transcript>
</video>
