<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<video>
    <resources><![CDATA[<p>There are no resources in this course.</p>]]>
    </resources>
    <transcript><![CDATA[
		<p><b>Coach: </b>Let’s take a look at the impact of not getting things right with performance planning. We’re going to meet Maya, a life insurance professional who had an idea of what she wanted to achieve, but despite being really busy, she always fell short of the target. We are going to hear from this life insurance professional how the Sales Manager helped her get back on track.</p>
		
		<p><b>Life insurance professional (Maya): </b>I suppose I thought if I concentrated on the sales activity – the phone calls and the meetings - the targets and the figures will be taken care of.</p>
		
		<p>I was working really hard. I was putting in a lot of effort. I thought I was doing really well – I was really busy. </p>
		
		<p>Trouble started when after a few weeks, I got a call from my manager. He was concerned that my actual number of policies was quite low and he was surprised that I’d not been sending him back full Sales Activity Reports and Summaries. </p>
		
		<p>Well, I’d been promising to get them to him, but I’d always put off doing them because I was busy making sales calls. </p>
		
		<p>I was really quite demoralized. I’d been working so hard, I’d put so much time and effort ... however, there were no results.</p>
		
		<p>My manager was really good at helping me get back on track. He was actually quite firm on where I’d gone wrong – pointing out that not only had I let myself down but I’d also made things difficult for him. We sat down, went through the need for clear activity input targets and careful tracking. We then looked at setting revised realistic targets for the next three months.</p>

		<p>By tracking the Business MIS, I started to notice what activity was paying off and what wasn’t. That brought back some confidence and sense of direction.</p>

		<p>The activity inputs reports and Business MIS help me to understand where I stand week by week and where I’m going. I’m pleased that I was able to come back on track while there was still time</p>

		<p>… and I’m set to achieve my overall targets for the year. </p>
    ]]>
    </transcript>
</video>
