<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<video>
    <resources><![CDATA[<p>There are no resources in this course.</p>]]>
    </resources>
    <transcript><![CDATA[
    	<p><b>Coach: </b>Measuring performance is an integral part of planning.
		You have to measure performance before you can do any planning.
		</p>
		
		<p>Measurement involves assessing your team’s current situation and past performance. Based on this measurement, you can plan your future sales targets and activity as well as decide where you need to intervene to review targets and provide additional training, coaching or other support. Regular meetings also ensure your team members are on track and visit the office regularly.</p>

		<p>You have to plan to succeed. No plan means there is no indication of whether you’ll have a successful year or not. You won’t know where you stand or how much you’ll earn.</p>

		<p>It’s the same with all businesses. You need to have some sort of accounting system and future projections. You need to know the exact position your business is in and where it will be in six months or a year. It may not be the most exciting area for some, but without it you can quickly find your business getting into trouble.</p>

		<p>In our business, if your life insurance professionals don’t plan enough time for prospecting, they will suddenly find themselves running out of potential customers and finally you will end up with idle life insurance professionals. </p>

		<p>You, as a Sales Manager, need a simple way of planning for the future and a way of tracking the performance of your life insurance professionals, in order to guide them in the right direction, if required.</p>

		<p>With the information in this module, you’ll be able to spot potential problems and shortfalls before they become too serious.</p>

		<p>You must plan and track your team’s performance, keep yourself and your team on target, and make sure you know where you and your team stand throughout the course of the year.</p>
    ]]>
    </transcript>
</video>