<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<video>
    <resources><![CDATA[<p>There are no resources in this course.</p>]]>
    </resources>
    <transcript><![CDATA[
		<p><b>Coach: </b>Both you and your team member need to monitor and record the sales performance ratios. </p>
		
		<p>It is critical that the mechanism for monitoring performance is included in the expectations you set with the life insurance professional. </p>
		
		<p>To do this, you need to:<br> 
			•	Ensure that the monthly targets are achieved so that you can see how well the life insurance professional is doing at any given point within the quarter.<br>
			•	Look out for any <b>trends</b>, <b>patterns and <b>issues</b> of underperformance - identifying these early on allows you to influence the performance by revising the plan.<br>
			•	Gain agreement on the completion and submission of the Sales Activity Report and Sales Activity Summary by the life insurance professional. <br>

		</p>
	
		<p>We’ve now covered all of the critical parts of the one-to-one planning meeting.</p>
		<p>We have seen the Sales Manager setting goals, planning sales activity and monitoring performance. Now remember, the one-to-one meeting is all about setting goals and expectations for the coming quarter. It’s essentially an agreement between the Sales Manager and the life insurance professional for the quarter ahead with everything geared towards meeting the overall target.</p>
		<p>In addition to your planned quarterly review meetings, you will also agree with the life insurance professional on the support levels for the coming three months. This means, for example:<br>
			•	New product training<br>
			•	One-to-one meetings<br>
			•	Joint fieldwork<br>
			•	Regular assessments <br>

		</p>

		<p>The frequency of this support depends on the life insurance professional’s level of experience and expertise. New and developing life insurance professionals will need to be supported more. You will need to meet with experienced life insurance professionals at least once a week. </p>
		

    ]]>
    </transcript>
</video>
