<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<video>
	<resources><![CDATA[<p>There are no resources in this course.</p>]]>
	</resources>
	<transcript><![CDATA[
        <p><b>Coach:</b> Performance management is a partnership between you and each life insurance professional. It is dependent upon the quality of the relationships you develop with your team. </p>
        <p>These relationships are important investing in your team members will make it easier to support and encourage them to be better at what they do.  </p>

        <p>These partnerships are about supporting and helping your team to be the best that they can be. </p>
        <p>Your role in this is vital. Your role is to inspire confidence, offer constant encouragement and maintain morale.  </p>
        <p>By working in partnership with your team, you will be able to help them be aware of and improve their strengths, as well as identify key areas for improvement. Specifically, you need to be able to:<br>
                •       Help them understand and improve their performance, <br>
                •       Give feedback which is both constructive and specific,<br>
                •       Help them to set objectives for improvement, and <br>
                •       Help them to make that improvement, whether through training or coaching.<br>
        </p>
        <p>Managing performance should be at the heart of what you do every single day.</p>
        <p>It’s an ongoing process, so you should be constantly talking to your people about their performance and development, be it offering feedback, giving guidance or asking them how they are doing. Make sure that you spend an appropriate amount of time with each life insurance professional depending on their experience and build this into your Model Week. Helping your team to achieve and maintain excellence will naturally help you to do the same.</p>
        <p>After recruiting the life insurance professionals that you needed to meet the sales target, managing their performance becomes an integral part of your role.</p>
        ]]>
	</transcript>
</video>
